Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Forest Guerrilla Battle
Episode 8
Golden Bulala
Where is it?
In my opinion
Golden Bulala is definitely in some special place
Look
It’s very special here
Strong wind
Help
Wolffy
are you okay
It seems like nothing here should be taken lightly.
what is that
Glowing Bulala
Could it be Golden Bulala
I’m finally going to find the legendary Golden Bulala
Be careful and let me help you up.
When did they become so close?
No idea.
There seemed to be some sound just now
Was it just my imagination?
You must have heard wrong
Let’s go
They are waiting for us
Good. go
Hurry up, son. We’re almost at Goats’ Village.
son
Don’t be afraid, Mommy is here
Don’t even think about hurting them
Brother Sparky
What is this?
Mr. Slowy. not good
Wolnie and Wilie are attacked by a strange monster
Sparky has already rushed up
What
What monster
It’s this monster
This is too dangerous
I’m going to help him
Wait for me
Wait
Kids, it’s more dangerous for you to go out without weapons.
But what about Wolnie and Wilie?
Planie, take out all the inventions of Gogoa
Uncle Gogoa’s props were taken for maintenance.
What about the Mysterious Ocean weapon set invented by Wolffy?
There’s a short circuit due to water ingress.
Then now I can only come up with my own inventions.
You’re talking about that invention
obey
This monster is really difficult to deal with
Brother Sparky, come on!
Wilie, be relieved
How could this monster possibly stump me?
Look at my Sparky’s attack
This is Golden Bulala
As long as you have it
The residents no longer have to be afraid of the monster.
Your wish for many years
is finally coming true
But how to use it
Watch out!
It’s strange. I’ve never seen such a monster before
It seems to be coming for Golden Bulala too
Run quickly
I’m holding on here
You guys go quickly
But
Go quickly
Watch me
let me help you
Weslie
Saving two handsome Weslies at once, cool
Thank you Wolffy
When it comes to rescuing people,
They are so in sync
It feels like they are the same person
I underestimated you
Looks like I should get serious
Now that you have the two fragments, come back.
Mr. Slowy, Sparky’s weapon is ready
ready
emission
Give my son back
Give the Golden Bulala back
Leave it to us
Stop
Still not working
here we come
Everyone, help pull it
I’m going to take the Golden Bulala out of its mouth
No, it’s too dangerous.
I have a shield, let me do it
It’s dangerous to do this
Believe me
Be careful
Give me back Sparky’s Golden Bulala
Weslie
I don’t want Golden Bulala anymore
Quickly let go
I didn’t know what courage was before
Until I got to know you guys
I slowly began to understand
I also have people I want to protect
So I’m not afraid of anything anymore
don’t touch him
let me go
Shrink!
Don’t even think about running away
Weslie
Golden Bulala
I only got one fragment
your hand
It’s okay, just sew it up and it’ll be fine
Do you not want your life?
Sorry, I couldn’t do it in the end
Thank you
Thank goodness you’re alright
It seems they really reconciled
I feel like they are better than before
This weapon is so cool
I defeated the monster alone
Sparky, thank you for saving Wilie
Brother Sparky, your equipment is really powerful.
What’s its name?
I don’t know either
But I feel like it has a protagonist aura
Let’s call it the Protagonist’s Aura.
Wilie
Are you okay, Wilie?
I’m fine
Why does the monster keep chasing Wilie?
this
Could it be that this thing attracted the monster here?
Let’s take it back and show it to Mr. Slowy.
To be continued